{
    "id": "5ec36a2b5c244312b376b8b55ddce9eb",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Get me the file ………………………… is on the table.",
            "description": "Either which or that can be used in identifying relative clauses to refer to things.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "049a37d5cba24d9293a7833514ec53ec"
        },
        {
            "question": "The house ………………………. she lived was very small.",
            "description": "Where can mean in which.",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "which",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b52cc5a9c53841319d83cc76050c2cd5"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy …………………………. fell into the well was rescued.",
            "description": "We use who to refer to people when the relative pronoun is the subject of the relative clause.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "54455ad3ddd941d191d9fc64d57177d2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The girl ………………………….. we met at the library is an aspiring writer.",
            "description": "We use whom when the relative pronoun is the object of the relative clause.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "011bfa892f2b4129ab49aa5828b6a280"
        },
        {
            "question": "Ravi, ……………………….. is my nephew, is  a brilliant student.",
            "description": "That cannot be used in non-identifying relative clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "83588544ffa3405cb1c50915a1a2eb52"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the dog ………………………… I was talking about.",
            "description": "Either that or which can refer to animals in identifying relative clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "61b83fc20ba94b1295b52bbb7e3b5b48"
        },
        {
            "question": "The exhibition ………………………….. was held in the town hall attracted tens of thousands of people.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "what",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8367a16946b1408bae04d44c94a01685"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where are the books ………………………. I left on the table?",
            "description": "Either that or which can refer to things in identifying relative clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c5ed52f761f8457c8aa6c27ca3312314"
        },
        {
            "question": "The man ………………………… car was stolen went to the police.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "who's",
                "whose"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0effe0067e8946cdafca1dfc4b8d8ff7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I know a girl …………………………. brother serves in the army.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "who's",
                "whose"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "57d3a59d288144679b8ebc468bb4aacb"
        },
        {
            "question": "The rope ………………………… was old snapped.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "what",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d4b86b7a81a74fc59e77eca7a303364c"
        }
    ]
}